[PING] June!
June!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Why aren't you answering?
June, where are you?
June!
- June!
- What's wrong?
[PING WHISPERING] Come here!
- [POT SHATTERS]
- [JUNE SCREAMS] Ack!
Listen carefully, June.
We need to call the police
immediately!
Huh?
[STUTTERING] Wh-- wh--
wh-- why?
What happened?
Uh... huh?!
Huh?
Oh!
[ZIA GRUNTS] I hate it!
That woman's always
getting in my way!
I have to eliminate
that gold digger
to get the old man's money.
Attorney!
Wrap it up already!
My brother already knows
everything!
Then I have no choice
but to push
the case against you
so you'll rot in jail!
I can finally return this
back to them.
You can't use me
against my brother anymore!
Then I'll just get rid of Ping!
I'm sick of you two!
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PANTING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
[SIGHS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello, Sheryn?
Are we ready for our next move?
Bring me to that person
who will knock June down.
[GRUNTS]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]